hey English Learners welcome to this A2
English listening practice video you can
use this video to practice your
listening comprehension and learn new
words and phrases today we're going to
talk about mourning people and night
people many of us consider ourselves
either a morning person or a night
person and we might have different
Lifestyles because of this but before we
start remember that you can practice
ractice your English listening with the
listening Time podcast on Spotify Apple
podcasts or on any other podcast app the
link to the listening Time Podcast is in
the description below okay let's talk
about morning people and night people
people are different in many ways and
one of the differences is whether they
prefer the morning or the night some
people love the morning they wake up
early and feel full of energy as soon
soon as the sun rises these are morning
people on the other hand there are those
that come alive when the moon is out
they're more active and alert during the
night these are night people let's dive
deeper into the preferences and habits
of both morning people and night people
morning folks often enjoy the quiet and
calm of the early morning hours they
like hearing birds chirping and maybe
seeing the sunrise this peaceful time
helps them start the day feeling good
making it easier to get things done for
them the morning is the best time to do
things they feel most productive when
the day is fresh and new many of them
like to get things done early so they
can relax later in the day night people
however find their peace or productivity
at night they might feel creative and
inspired while other people are already
in bed at that that time they can focus
on their thoughts and projects without
getting easily distracted nighttime is
precious to them for hobbies studying
working or other things in terms of
spending time with others morning people
tend to plan activities for the earlier
part of the day they enjoy socializing
during daylight hours such as having
brunch with friends or going on a
morning walk with someone they might
feel closer to people who ALS Al enjoy
getting up early night people however
prefer social events later in the day
they feel more energetic and social as
the day goes on night people might enjoy
going to dinner with friends chatting
late into the night or going to concerts
they often have friends who also prefer
nighttime activities so what are some
advantages and disadvantages of being a
morning person or a night person one one
of the best things about being a morning
person is that the day usually feels
longer when you wake up earlier it can
feel like you have more time to do
things the earlier I wake up the more
things I do during my day however one
disadvantage of being a morning person
is that you might get really sleepy
later in the day if you wake up really
early you're probably going to get tired
early how about night people
well one advantage of being a night
person is that you can often socialize
more with other people after people
finish their workday there's still time
to hang out with family and friends
before the day is over they go to bed
later so they have more time in the
evening and most people socialize after
work not before work however one
disadvantage of being a night person
might be your sleep schedule many many
night people still have to wake up early
on weekdays so this means they might
sleep less and how about you are you a
morning person or a night person leave a
comment and let me know okay I hope you
enjoyed this listening practice video
remember to download my free listening
Time Podcast if you want to practice
your English the link is in the
description below and you can also join
my membership if you want my training to
help you understand fast English that
link is also down below all right thank
you for watching and I'll talk to you in
the next
video